Inventory of the Resistencia Nicaragüense Ejército records
Hoover Institution Archives
Resistencia Nicaragüense Ejército records
1979-1993
94002
Hoover Institution Archives
130 manuscript boxes (54.2 linear feet)
Reports, correspondence, memoranda, press releases, rosters, personnel records, statistics, financial records, and photographs relating to guerrilla military operations in Nicaragua, financing and supply of guerrilla forces, medical care and administration of justice in guerrilla-controlled areas, truce violations following the end of the war, and Nicaraguan refugees in Honduras. Includes records of the predecessor Fuerza Democrática Nicaragüense. Also on microfilm (136 reels).
Resistencia Nicaragüense (Organization). Ejército.
Fuerza Democrática Nicaragüense.
Access
Closed. Microfilm (Reels 1-44) of a portion of the collection available for use. Users must sign use agreement.
The Hoover Institution Archives only allows access to copies of audiovisual items, computer media, and digital files. To listen to sound recordings or to view videos, films, or digital files during your visit, please contact the Archives at least two working days before your arrival. We will then advise you of the accessibility of the material you wish to see or hear. Please note that not all material is immediately accessible.
Acquisition Information
Acquired by the Hoover Institution Archives in 1994.
Accruals
Materials may have been added to the collection since this finding aid was prepared. To determine if this has occurred, find the collection in Stanford University's online catalog at http://searchworks.stanford.edu/. Materials have been added to the collection if the number of boxes listed in the online catalog is larger than the number of boxes listed in this finding aid.
Alternative Forms of Material Available
Also on microfilm (136 reels).
Historical Note
Nicaraguan resistance army engaged in guerrilla warfare against the Sandinista government of Nicaragua.
Scope and Content of Collection
Reports, correspondence, memoranda, press releases, rosters, personnel records, statistics, financial records, and photographs relating to guerrilla military operations in Nicaragua, financing and supply of guerrilla forces, medical care and administration of justice in guerrilla-controlled areas, truce violations following the end of the war, and Nicaraguan refugees in Honduras. Includes records of the predecessor Fuerza Democrática Nicaragüense. Also on microfilm (136 reels).
Note: The following abbreviations are used throughout the list: C.R.: Comando Regional F.T.: Fuerza de Tarea
Guerrillas--Nicaragua.; Nicaragua--History--1979-1990.; Nicaraguans--Honduras.; Refugees.
- CLOSED (Box-folder 1: 1-2)
- Base Ariel: rosters, 1982 (Box-folder 1: 3-4)
- Base Ariel: lists of ex-Guardia Nacional personnel, equipment lists, undated (Box-folder 1: 5)
- Base Ariel: messages, rosters, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 1: 6)
- Base Fénix, Base Rus-Rus, Base del Frente Rafael Domingo, Base de Los Raudales: rosters, reports, state of force reports, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 1: 7)
- Base Fénix, other units: rosters, state of force reports, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 1: 8)
- Base Fénix: letters, 1982-1984 (Box-folder 1: 9)
- Base Nicarao: messages, rosters, reports, state of force reports, casualty reports, 1982-1984 (Box-folder 2: 1)
- Base Pino I, Centro de Operaciones Tácticas del Atlantico: rosters, reports, personnel data sheets, messages, 1982 (Box-folder 2: 2)
- Base Pino I, Base Francisco Morazán: messages, rosters, state of force reports, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 2: 3)
- Base Pino I: weapons assignment lists, 1983 (Box-folder 2: 4)
- Base Sagitario: rosters, 1981 (Box-folder 2: 5)
- Base Sagitario: rosters (2 notebooks in 1 folder), 1982 (Box-folder 2: 6)
- Base Sagitario: rosters, lists of dependents, equipment lists, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 2: 7)
- Base Sagitario: rosters, state of force reports, weapons assignment lists, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 2: 8)
- Base Sagitario: messages, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 2: 9)
- Base Sagitario, Estado Mayor: code keys, guard duty assignment lists, messages, rosters, printed matter, miscellany, 1982-1984 (Box-folder 2: 10)
- Base Zebra: rosters, state of force reports, 1979-1982 (Box-folder 3: 1)
- Base Zebra: rosters, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 3: 2)
- Base Zebra, Base Francisco Morazán: rosters, messages, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 3: 3)
- Base Zebra: messages, 1982 (Box-folder 3: 4)
- Base Zebra: messages, personnel data sheets, 1983 (Box-folder 3: 5)
- Base Escuela: messages, rosters, state of force reports, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 3: 6)
- C.R. Manuel Alzugaray: rosters, lists of personnel infiltrated and returned, 1989 (Box-folder 3: 7)
- C.R. Manuel Alzugaray, 3er Comando Operacional: rosters, lists of personnel infiltrated and returned, weapons assignment lists, 1989 (Box-folder 3: 8)
- C.R. Manuel Alzugaray, 3er Comando Operacional: lists of personnel infiltrated and returned, 1990 (Box-folder 3: 9)
- C.R. Manuel Alzugaray: messages, 1990 (Box-folder 3: 10)
- C.R. Ismael Castillo: rosters, state of force reports, weapons assignment lists, lists of personnel infiltrated and returned, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 3: 11)
- C.R. Ismael Castillo: rosters, lists of personnel infiltrated and returned, 1989 (Box-folder 3: 12)
- C.R. Ismael Castillo: lists of personnel infiltrated and returned, 1990 (Box-folder 3: 13)
- C.R. Ismael Castillo: casualty reports, 1989 (Box-folder 3: 14)
- C.R. Ismael Castillo, 4to Comando Operacional: messages, 1990 (Box-folder 3: 15)
- C.R. Andrés Castro: rosters, state of force reports, lists of personnel infiltrated and returned, 1989 (Box-folder 4: 1)
- C.R. Andrés Castro: rosters, lists of personnel infiltrated and returned, 1990 (Box-folder 4: 2)
- C.R. Andrés Castro: messages, 1990 (Box-folder 4: 3)
- C.R. Juan Castro: rosters, 1984 (Box-folder 4: 4)
- Centro de Operaciones Tácticas del Atlantico: rosters, personnel data sheets, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 4: 5)
- C.R. Comando de Operaciones Tácticas, C.R. Jose Dolores Estrada: rosters, weapons assignment lists, 1984 (Box-folder 4: 6)
- C.R. Comando de Operaciones Tácticas: rosters, weapons assignment lists, lists of personnel infiltrated and returned, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 4: 7)
- C.R. Comando de Operaciones Tácticas, unidentified units: rosters, lists of personnel infiltrated and returned, 1988 (Box-folder 4: 8)
- C.R. Comando de Operaciones Tácticas: rosters, state of force reports, lists of personnel infiltrated and returned, weapons assignment lists, 1989 (Box-folder 4: 9)
- C.R. Comando de Operaciones Tácticas, 2do Comando Operacional: rosters, lists of personnel infiltrated and returned, 1989 (Box-folder 4: 10)
- C.R. Comando de Operaciones Tácticas, 2do Comando Operacional: lists of personnel infiltrated and returned, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 4: 11)
- C.R. Comando de Operaciones Tácticas: messages, 1990 (Box-folder 4: 12)
- C.R. Jose Dolores Estrada, C.R. Basilio Garmendia, C.R. Pedro J. Gonzáles: lists of personnel infiltrated and returned, rosters, personnel memoranda, 1989 (Box-folder 4: 13)
- C.R. Jose Dolores Estrada: casualty lists, 1988 (Box-folder 4: 14)
- F.T. Oscar Montenegro (C.R. Jose Dolores Estrada): rosters, undated (Box-folder 4: 15)
- C.R. Humberto Galeano: rosters, weapons assignment lists, lists of personnel infiltrated and returned, 1989 (Box-folder 4: 16)
- C.R. Humberto Galeano: casualty lists, 1988 (Box-folder 4: 17)
- C.R. Pedro J. Gonzáles: rosters, personnel data sheet, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 4: 18)
- C.R. Pedro J. Gonzáles: rosters, weapons assignment lists, lists of personnel infiltrated and returned, personnel memoranda, 1986 (Box-folder 4: 19)
- C.R. Pedro J. Gonzáles, 3er Comando Operacional: rosters, state of force reports, lists of personnel infiltrated and returned, 1989 (Box-folder 4: 20)
- C.R. Pedro J. Gonzáles, 3er Comando Operacional: weapons assignment lists, lists of personnel infiltrated and returned, state of force report, 1989 (Box-folder 4: 21)
- C.R. Pedro J. Gonzáles, 3er Comando Operacional: lists of personnel infiltrated and returned, rosters, 1990 (Box-folder 4: 22)
- C.R. Pedro J. Gonzáles: messages, 1990 (Box-folder 4: 23-24)
- C.R. Rafael Herrera, C.R. Alonso Irias, C.R. 15 de Septiembre, C.R. Quilalí, F.T. Raul Arroliga, Grupo de Zapadores, Banda Marcial, miscellaneous units: rosters, reports, memoranda, letters, personnel data sheets, miscellany, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 5: 1)
- C.R. Rafael Herrera: rosters, lists of personnel infiltrated and returned, 1986 (Box-folder 5: 2)
- C.R. Rafael Herrera, C.R. Quilalí: rosters, state of force reports, weapons assignment lists, 1987 (Box-folder 5: 3)
- C.R. Rafael Herrera: lists of personnel at Centro de Instrucción Militar training, 1984 (Box-folder 5: 4)
- C.R. Rafael Herrera: lists of captured personnel, 1990 (Box-folder 5: 5)
- C.R. Rafael Herrera: personnel memoranda, code key, undated (Box-folder 5: 6)
- C.R. Alonso Irias: rosters, 1986 (Box-folder 5: 7)
- C.R. Alonso Irias: rosters, state of force reports, 1987 (Box-folder 5: 8)
- C.R. Alonso Irias, C.R. Domingo Rivera: rosters, weapons assignment lists, 1989 (Box-folder 5: 9)
- C.R. Larry McDonald: rosters, weapons assignment lists, personnel infiltrated and returned, 1986 (Box-folder 5: 10)
- C.R. Larry McDonald: rosters, state of force reports, lists of personnel infiltrated and returned, casualty lists, 1987 (Box-folder 5: 11)
- C.R. Larry McDonald, C.R. Trinidad Poveda López: rosters, state of force reports, weapons assignment lists, lists of personnel infiltrated and returned, personnel memoranda, 1989 (Box-folder 5: 12)
- C.R. Santiago Meza: rosters, weapons assignment lists, 1986 (Box-folder 5: 13)
- C.R. Santiago Meza, C.R. Jorge Salazar #5, C.R. Nicarao, F.T. Raul Arroliga: rosters, state of force reports, weapons assignment lists, 1989 (Box-folder 5: 14)
- C.R. Santiago Meza, ler Comando Operacional: rosters, 1989 (Box-folder 5: 15)
- C.R. Santiago Meza: lists of personnel infiltrated and returned, 1990 (Box-folder 5: 16)
- C.R. Santiago Meza: weapons assignment lists, 1986 (Box-folder 5: 17)
- C.R. Santiago Meza: personnel memoranda, 1990 (Box-folder 5: 18)
- C.R. Santiago Meza: lists of personnel unfit for duty, lists of dependents, 1990 (Box-folder 5: 19)
- C.R. Santiago Meza: lists of personnel unfit for duty, lists of dependents, undated (Box-folder 5: 20)
- C.R. Santiago Meza: list of wounded personnel, list of female personnel, 1990 (Box-folder 5: 21)
- C.R. Santiago Meza: lists of children, undated (Box-folder 5: 22)
- C.R. Nicarao: rosters, state of force reports, casualty lists, weapons assignment lists, personnel data sheets, personnel memoranda, equipment lists, 1982-1986 (Box-folder 6: 1)
- C.R. Nicarao, miscellaneous units: rosters, personnel memoranda, 1984-1987 (Box-folder 6: 2)
- C.R. Nicarao: rosters, lists of personnel infiltrated and returned, personnel memoranda, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 6: 3)
- C.R. Nicarao: state of force reports, lists of personnel infiltrated and returned, personnel data sheet, personnel memoranda, 1987 (Box-folder 6: 4)
- C.R. Nicarao: lists of personnel killed, 1987 (Box-folder 6: 5)
- C.R. Nicarao: lists of personnel completing training courses, state of force report, 1984 (Box-folder 6: 6)
- C.R. Nicarao: lists of ex-Sandinista personnel, 1986 (Box-folder 6: 7)
- F.T. Monimbo (C.R. Nicarao): rosters, weapons assignment lists, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 6: 8)
- C.R. 15 de Septiembre, Fuerza marina, miscellaneous units: rosters, weapons assignment lists, lists of personnel infiltrated and returned, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 6: 9)
- C.R. 15 de Septiembre, ler Comando Operacional: rosters, weapons assignment lists, lists of personnel infiltrated and returned, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 6: 10)
- C.R. 15 de Septiembre, ler Comando Operacional: rosters, lists of personnel infiltrated and returned, personnel memoranda, 1989 (Box-folder 6: 11)
- C.R. 15 de Septiembre: state of force reports, lists of personnel infiltrated and returned, 1987 (Box-folder 6: 12)
- C.R. 15 de Septiembre: lists of personnel infiltrated and returned, 1990 (Box-folder 6: 13-14)
- C.R. 15 de Septiembre: messages, 1990 (Box-folder 6: 15-16)
- C.R. San Jacinto: rosters, messages, lists of personnel infiltrated and returned, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 7: 1)
- C. R. San Jacinto: rosters, lists of personnel infiltrated and returned, 1986 (Box-folder 7: 2)
- C.R. San Jacinto: rosters, 1987 (Box-folder 7: 3)
- C.R. San Jacinto: rosters, state of force reports, lists of dependents, lists of female personnel, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 7: 4)
- C.R. San Jacinto, C.R. Jorge Salazar #3: rosters, lists of personnel infiltrated and returned, lists of dependents, weapons assignment lists, 1989 (Box-folder 7: 5)
- C.R. San Jacinto: roster, training schedule, 1989 (Box-folder 7: 6)
- C.R. San Jacinto: rosters, weapons assignment lists, lists of personnel infiltrated and returned, 1990 (Box-folder 7: 7)
- C.R. San Jacinto: lists of personnel infiltrated and returned, lists of dependents, 1990 (Box-folder 7: 8)
- C.R. San Jacinto: list of prisoners released by Sandinistas, 1989 (Box-folder 7: 9)
- C.R. San Jacinto: messages, 1990 (Box-folder 7: 10)
- C.R. Salvador Pereéz, F.T. Leonardo Palma (C.R. Andrés Castro): personnel data sheets, rosters, lists of personnel infiltrated and returned, 1985 (Box-folder 7: 11)
- C.R. Salvador Pereéz: personnel data sheets, undated (Box-folder 7: 12)
- C.R. Salvador Pereéz: rosters, weapons assignment lists, lists of personnel infiltrated and returned, lists of personnel at Centro de Instrucción Militar training, 1986 (Box-folder 7: 13)
- C.R. Salvador Pereéz: rosters, state of force reports, lists of personnel infiltrated and returned, weapons assignment lists, 1987 (Box-folder 7: 14)
- C.R. Salvador Pereéz, C.R. Basilio Garmendia: rosters, lists of personnel infiltrated and returned, weapons assignment lists, 1989 (Box-folder 7: 15)
- C.R. Salvador Pereéz: messages, 1990 (Box-folder 7: 16)
- C.R. Quilalí: personnel data sheets, undated (Box-folder 7: 17)
- C.R. Quilalí: rosters, state of force reports, weapons assignment lists, lists of personnel infiltrated and returned, casualty lists, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 7: 18)
- C.R. Quilalí: rosters, weapons assignment lists, lists of personnel infiltrated and returned, 1989 (Box-folder 7: 19)
- C.R. Quilalí, C.R. Santiago Meza: list of female personnel, list of children, list of personnel unfit for duty, undated (Box-folder 7: 20)
- C.R. Quilalí: list of personnel infiltrated and returned, 1986 (Box-folder 7: 21)
- C.R. Quilalí: lists of personnel killed, 1989 (Box-folder 7: 22)
- C.R. Quilalí: report, deposition, 1987 (Box-folder 7: 23)
- C.R. Jorge Salazar, C.R. Comando de Operaciones Tácticas, Base Nicarao: rosters, weapons assignment lists, state of force report, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 7: 24)
- C.R. Jorge Salazar #1, C.R. Jorge Salazar #2, C.R. Jorge Salazar #3, C.R. Jorge Salazar #4, C.R. Jorge Salazar #5: data sheets for staff officers at Centro de Instrucción Militar training, 1987 (Box-folder 8: 1)
- C.R. Jorge Salazar #1, C.R. Comando de Operaciones Tácticas: personnel data sheets, personnel memoranda, miscellany, 1987 (Box-folder 8: 2)
- C.R. Jorge Salazar #1: rosters, weapons assignment lists, list of wounded personnel, 1986 (Box-folder 8: 3)
- C.R. Jorge Salazar #1, Fuerza Aérea: rosters, personnel memoranda, parachutist certificate, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 8: 4)
- C.R. Jorge Salazar #1, 5to Comando Operacional: rosters, state of force reports, 1987-1989 (Box-folder 8: 5)
- C.R. Jorge Salazar #1, 5to Comando Operacional: rosters, 1989 (Box-folder 8: 6)
- C.R. Jorge Salazar #1, 5to Comando Operacional: rosters, weapons assignment lists, lists of personnel infiltrated and returned, 1989 (Box-folder 8: 7)
- C.R. Jorge Salazar #1, 5to Comando Operacional: rosters, lists of personnel infiltrated and returned, list of personnel at Centro de Instrucción Militar training, 1990 (Box-folder 8: 8)
- C.R. Jorge Salazar #1: casualty lists, 1988 (Box-folder 8: 9)
- C.R. Jorge Salazar #1: messages, 1990 (Box-folder 8: 10)
- C.R. Jorge Salazar #2: rosters, weapons assignment list, list of personnel at Centro de Instrucción Militar training, 1987 (Box-folder 8: 11)
- C.R. Jorge Salazar #2: rosters, state of force reports, lists of personnel infiltrated and returned, list of deserters, list of hospitalized personnel, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 8: 12)
- C.R. Jorge Salazar #2, 5to Comando Operacional: rosters, lists of personnel infiltrated and returned, list of dependents, 1989 (Box-folder 8: 13)
- C.R. Jorge Salazar #2, C.R. Jorge Salazar #1, C.R. Comando de Operaciones Tácticas, C.R. Basilio Garmendia: rosters, lists of personnel at Centro de Instrucción Militar training, 1989 (Box-folder 8: 14)
- C.R. Jorge Salazar #2, 5to Comando Operacional: rosters, lists of personnel infiltrated and returned, list of children, 1990 (Box-folder 8: 15)
- C.R. Jorge Salazar #2: lists of personnel killed, 1989 (Box-folder 8: 16-17)
- C.R. Jorge Salazar #2: messages, 1990 (Box-folder 8: 18)
- C.R. Jorge Salazar #3, C.R. Jorge Salazar #1, C.R. Jorge Salazar #2: rosters, state of force reports, weapons assignment lists, lists of personnel infiltrated and returned, 1987 (Box-folder 8: 19)
- C.R. Jorge Salazar #3, 5to Comando Operacional: rosters, 1989 (Box-folder 8: 20)
- C.R. Jorge Salazar #3, 5to Comando Operacional: rosters, state of force report, list of personnel infiltrated and returned, 1990 (Box-folder 8: 21)
- C.R. Jorge Salazar #3: message, 1990 (Box-folder 8: 22)
- C.R. Jorge Salazar #4, C.R. Comando de Operaciones Tácticas, Batallón Apoyo Auxiliar, Comando Estratégico: personnel data sheets, infiltration and return log, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 8: 23)
- C.R. Jorge Salazar #4: rosters, 1987 (Box-folder 8: 24-25)
- C.R. Jorge Salazar #4: rosters, weapons assignment lists, lists of personnel infiltrated and returned, personnel memoranda, 1989 (Box-folder 8: 26)
- C.R. Jorge Salazar #4, 4to Comando Operacional: rosters, 1989 (Box-folder 9: 1)
- C.R. Jorge Salazar #4, 4to Comando Operacional: rosters, weapons assignment lists, 1990 (Box-folder 9: 2)
- C.R. Jorge Salazar #4: lists of personnel killed, 1989 (Box-folder 9: 3)
- C.R. Jorge Salazar #4: message, 1990 (Box-folder 9: 4)
- C.R. Jorge Salazar #5, 4to Comando Operacional: rosters, 1989 (Box-folder 9: 5-6)
- C.R. Jorge Salazar #5, 4to Comando Operacional: rosters, lists of personnel infiltrated and returned, 1990 (Box-folder 9: 7)
- C.R. Jorge Salazar #5: lists of personnel killed, 1988 (Box-folder 9: 8)
- C.R. Jorge Salazar #5: messages, 1990 (Box-folder 9: 9)
- C.R. Segovia: rosters, memoranda, state of force reports, personnel data sheets, 1985 (Box-folder 9: 10)
- C.R. Segovia: rosters, lists of personnel infiltrated and returned, weapons assignment lists, 1985 (Box-folder 9: 11)
- C.R. Segovia: rosters, weapons assignment lists, memoranda, 1986 (Box-folder 9: 12)
- C.R. Segovia: rosters, memoranda, 1987 (Box-folder 9: 13)
- C.R. Segovia: rosters, lists of personnel infiltrated and returned, weapons assignment lists, personnel memoranda, 1987 (Box-folder 9: 14)
- C.R. Segovia: roster, 1989 (Box-folder 9: 15)
- C.R. Segovia, C.R. Nicarao, ler Comando Operacional: rosters, lists of personnel infiltrated and returned, memoranda, messages, 1989 (Box-folder 9: 16)
- C.R. Segovia, ler Comando Operacional: lists of personnel infiltrated and returned, 1990 (Box-folder 9: 17)
- C.R. Segovia: lists of female personnel, lists of wounded personnel, lists of widows and orphans, 1990 (Box-folder 9: 18)
- C.R. Segovia: messages, memoranda, personnel data sheet, miscellany, 1984 (Box-folder 9: 19)
- F.T. Yali (C.R. Segovia): rosters, state of force reports, lists of female personnel, lists of dependents, casualty lists, 1988 (Box-folder 9: 20)
- C.R. Guillermo Castro, C.R. Domingo Rivera: lists of personnel infiltrated and returned rosters, weapons assignment lists, 1989 (Box-folder 10: 1)
- C.R. Guillermo Castro: lists of personnel killed, 1989 (Box-folder 10: 2)
- C.R. Basilio Garmendia, C.R. Trinidad Poveda López, 2do Comando Operacional: lists of personnel infiltrated and returned, rosters, personnel memoranda, 1989-1900 (Box-folder 10: 3)
- C.R. Basilio Garmendia: messages, 1990 (Box-folder 10: 4)
- C.R. Jose Miguel Moncada, 2do Comando Operacional: rosters, state of force reports, lists of wounded personnel, lists of female personnel, lists of children, 1989 (Box-folder 10: 5)
- C.R. Jose Miguel Moncada: list of personnel killed, 1989 (Box-folder 10: 6)
- C.R. Trinidad Poveda López, 2do Comando Operacional: lists of personnel infiltrated and returned, rosters, state of force reports, lists of female personnel, personnel memoranda, 1989 (Box-folder 10: 7)
- C.R. Trinidad Poveda López, C.R. Quilalí, 2do Comando Operacional: lists of personnel infiltrated and returned, personnel memoranda, 1988-1990 (Box-folder 10: 8)
- C.R. Trinidad Poveda López: messages, 1990 (Box-folder 10: 9)
- C.R. Domingo Rivera, C.R. Salvador Pereéz: messages, 1990 (Box-folder 10: 10)
- C.R. Esteban Rizo Moran: rosters, state of force reports, lists of personnel infiltrated and returned, weapons assignment lists, personnel memoranda, 1989 (Box-folder 10: 11)
- C.R. Esteban Rizo Moran, 4to Comando Operacional: rosters, personnel memoranda, 1989 (Box-folder 10: 12)
- C.R. Esteban Rizo Moran, 4to Comando Operacional: lists of personnel infiltrated and returned, 1990 (Box-folder 10: 13)
- C.R. Esteban Rizo Moran: messages, 1990 (Box-folder 10: 14)
- 2do Comando Operacional, C.R. Comando de Operaciones Tácticas, C.R. Basilio Garmendia, C.R. Salvador Pereéz, C.R. Trinidad Poveda López: rosters, lists of wounded personnel, lists of female personnel, lists of children, 1989 (Box-folder 10: 15)
- 2do Comando Operacional, C.R. Basilio Garmendia: rosters, lists of personnel infiltrated and returned, 1989 (Box-folder 10: 16)
- 2do Comando Operacional: lists of personnel infiltrated and returned, personnel memoranda, 1990 (Box-folder 10: 17)
- 3er Comando Operacional, C.R. Domingo Rivera: rosters, weapons assignment lists, lists of personnel infiltrated and returned, 1989 (Box-folder 10: 18)
- 4to Comando Operacional, 5to Comando Operacional, C.R. Ismael Castillo, C.R. Esteban Rizo Moran, C.R. Jorge Salazar #1, C.R. Jorge Salazar #2, C.R. Jorge Salazar #3, C.R. Jorge Salazar #4, C.R. Jorge Salazar #5, rosters, weapons assignment lists, lists of personnel infiltrated and returned, lists of female personnel, lists of children, 1990 (Box-folder 10: 19)
- Grupo Abel: weapons assignment lists, 1987 (Box-folder 10: 20)
- CLOSED (Box-folder 10: 21)
- Fuerza Marina: rosters, undated (Box-folder 11: 1)
- F.T. Milton Fritz: weapons assignment lists, state of force reports, 1986 (Box-folder 11: 2)
- F.T. Independencia: personnel data sheets, undated (Box-folder 11: 3)
- F.T. Independencia: rosters, weapons assignment lists, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 11: 4)
- F.T. Raul Arroliga: rosters, weapons assignment lists, lists of personnel infiltrated and returned, 1986 (Box-folder 11: 5)
- F.T. Jose Adán Sevilla: rosters, 1987 (Box-folder 11: 6)
- F.T. Jose Adán Sevilla: roster, 1988 (Box-folder 11: 7)
- F.T. Jose Adán Sevilla: rosters, lists of personnel infiltrated and returned, personnel memoranda, 1989 (Box-folder 11: 8)
- Grupo Zebra: rosters, 1985 (Box-folder 11: 9)
- Unidad de Artillería, Sub-Centro de Suministros: rosters, equipment list, 1987 (Box-folder 11: 10)
- Unidad de Artillería: rosters, state of force reports, lists of personnel at Centro de Instrucción Militar training, lists of female personnel, lists of children, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 11: 11)
- Unidad de Artillería: rosters, memoranda, lists of personnel infiltrated and returned, lists of female personnel, 1990 (Box-folder 11: 12)
- Base Aguacate: memoranda, 1987 (Box-folder 11: 13)
- Base San Andrés de Bocay: rosters, state of force reports, personnel memoranda, 1988 (Box-folder 11: 14)